couple.me 2019-05-28

# Couple - Privacy

## TenthBit Privacy Policy

#### Last updated: October 5, 2015

Your privacy is critically important to us. Our privacy policy will explain how personal information is collected, used and disclosed by TenthBit Inc. (TenthBit) with respect to your access and use of TenthBit’s web site couple.me, mobile applications and services (“Couple ”).

If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [support@tenthbit.com](mailto:support@tenthbit.com).

Our privacy policy may be modified from time-to-time. We will alert you that changes have been made by indicating on our privacy policy the date it was last updated. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on this web site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### What is Personal Information?

"Personal Information” is personally identifiable information such as your name, telephone number and email address and any other non-public information about you that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing information. Personal information does not include "aggregate" information, which is data we collect about the use of Couple. Our privacy policy does not restrict or limit our collection and use of aggregate information.

### What Personal Information Do We Collect?

We actively collect certain information you voluntarily provide to us including but not limited to:

  * your name,
  * email address,
  * birthday and anniversary dates,
  * and phone number

when you create an account, send us an email or submit content to the Couple.

We automatically collect certain information when you use Couple, such as:

  * your Internet Protocol (IP) address,
  * your device type, and
  * your operating system version.

We treat this information as personal information if we combine it with or link it to any of the identifying information mentioned above. Otherwise, it is used in the aggregate only.

When you download and use our Services, we automatically collect information on:

  * the type of device you use,
  * operating system version,
  * and the device identifier (or "UDID").

We also collect your location-based information for the purpose of:

  * attaching location information to photos and videos,
  * reminding users of memories they've had in various places,
  * providing search services for user memories using location information,
  * or sharing location data with the person you are connected with.

We will only share this information with our mapping provider for the sole purpose of providing you this service. You may opt-out of location-based services at any time by editing the setting at the device level or by emailing us at support@tenthbit.com.

As part of our service, we ask that you request a friend to join. We will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend an email inviting them to visit the service, with a one-time follow up email thereafter . We store this information so that you will be connected to each other when using the service. Your friend may contact us to request that we remove this information from our database.

### How Do We Use the Personal Information We Collect?

Generally, we collect, store, use and disclose information to enable us to:

  * provide Couple,
  * create your account,
  * identify you as a user,
  * respond to your inquiries and emails,
  * improve the Couple,
  * send you administrative and service related communications,
  * and send you newsletters, surveys, offers, and other promotional materials.

Anonymous aggregate statistics that do not personally identify a Couple user will be kept and used by us for various purposes including analysis and reporting of usage patterns. TenthBit reserves the right to use and disclose anonymous aggregate statistics for any purpose and to any third party in its sole discretion.

### What Do We Share With Third Parties?

From time to time we may employ third parties to help us provide or improve Couple. These third parties, such as our analytics or hosting provider, may have limited access to databases of user information or registered member information solely for the purpose of helping us provide or improve the Couple and they will not be able to use the information about our members or visitors for any other purpose. We also may share your information with other companies which are owned by the or under the same ownership as our company.

We may disclose Personal Information in some other limited circumstances, but we will specifically describe them to you when we collect the information, such as in the terms of use for a new service or by revising this Privacy Policy.

We may, and you hereby authorize us to, disclose your Personal Information (including messages) to a third party without your consent:

  * if we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other website users, or anyone else (including the rights or property of anyone else) that could be harmed by such activities,
  * in connection with any legal investigation,
  * when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is required by and in accordance with the law or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on TenthBit,
  * to any third party with your prior consent to do so,
  * to other parties in connection with a company transaction, such as a merger, sale of company assets or shares, reorganization, financing, change of control or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company or third party or in the event of a bankruptcy or related or similar proceedings. 

### Control Over Content

Aside from what is set forth in our privacy policy, we will store any content submitted to Couple for the sole purpose of displaying that content only to the person with whom you are paired, or for whom you are currently waiting to accept your pair request, at the time of submission. Your content will only be accessed by Tenthbit, Inc. employees for the purposes of technical support. When you make a request for technical support that may require us to access your content, we will notify you and seek permission before accessing your timeline.

### Links to Other Sites

When you click on a link to any other website or location, you will leave Couple and go to another site and another entity may collect Personal Information or anonymous data from you. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for, these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites or content, or to any collection of data after you click on links to such outside websites.

### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us. We use reasonable efforts to store and maintain your Personal Information and location information in a secure environment and have implemented reasonable procedures designed to limit unauthorized access, use or disclosure of your Personal Information. We encrypt the transmission location information of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Despite these measures, you should know that TenthBit cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

You are also responsible for helping to protect the security of your Personal Information. To protect the communications that have taken place in the app, never give out your password. To increase device-level security, set a Security Code in the Couple’s settings.

### User Access and Choice

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service , you may email us at [support@tenthbit.com](mailto:support@tenthbit.com) to deactivate your account. You may also correct, update, or amend your personal information in your profile settings within Couple or by emailing us at [support@tenthbit.com](mailto:support@tenthbit.com).

Removing Couple from your mobile device will not delete the personal information we have retained about you. If you unpair from your partner, we will retain your user content in the event that you would like to access in the future. Your user content can be deleted permanently by emailing a request to [support@tenthbit.com](mailto:support@tenthbit.com).

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Communication With TenthBit

You may "opt out" of receiving marketing or promotional emails from us by following the instructions in those emails or by emailing us at [support@tenthbit.com](mailto:support@tenthbit.com). If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your accounts or our ongoing business relations. To opt out of push notifications, please edit settings within the app or change your settings at the device level.

### Tracking Technologies We Collect

We use cookies on this site. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our site.

  * We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies.
  * A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A session ID cookie remembers that you are logged in.
  * A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. A persistent cookie saves your individual preferences next time that you log in. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “Help” directory.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

Our third party partners employ clear gifs, images, and scripts that help them better manage content on our site. We do not tie the information gathered to our users personal information.

### Social Media Widgets

Our web site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the ShareThis button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our web site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Blog

Our web site offers publicly accessible blogs and community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. You can request the removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum by contacting us at [support@tenthbit.com](mailto:support@tenthbit.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

### International Users

Couple is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to users in the United States. If you are a user accessing Couple from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of Couple, which is governed by U.S. law, the TenthBit Privacy Policy, and the TenthBit Terms of Service, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

### Questions?

Please contact us at [support@tenthbit.com](mailto:support@tenthbit.com) if you have any questions about our privacy policy.

TenthBit, Inc. 59 Grant Avenue, Suite 300 San Francisco, CA 94108 U.S.A.
